it's great to be in your energy again
bishar well thank youna good day to you
thank you it's uh I'm gonna choose to
speak technical today technical all
right so continuing from our previous
conversation earlier this year uh I'm
left with questions about gravity yes
and about the um the nested capacitor
design yes so uh we spoke about the
prime radiant yes and it's relationship
to the you just lost half the
audience you wish to explain then Prime
radiant very briefly is simply the idea
that if you imagine and this is just an
analogy imagine a single particle in all
of existence if you wish imagine one
tiny little subatomic particle in a big
black void nothing else exists this one
tiny particle because it's the only
thing has no rules it can go as fast as
it wants if it travels thus then at
infinite speed throughout this black
void in whatever pattern it wishes it
will appear to be many particles all at
once because it's going so fast it can
appear next to itself over and over and
over again at the same time this is how
reality is structured and that's why you
literally are made of the same thing
that everyone and everything else is
this is the prime radiant idea from our
civilization please continue correct so
you spoke about structure yes um and in
our conversation we ALS well we related
the prime radiant to gravity in a sense
yes there is an aspect of that obviously
that creates what you experience as
gravity yes okay so in the idea of the F
the fabric of space and time gra gravity
appears to be an energy of higher
vibrational quality why because it bends
it well so to speak yes at least to our
modern day scientists um and it's still
very misunderstood yes or highly non
understood yes so could you expand on
the u a little more on the nature of
gravity how to create it handle it
harness it and manipulated turn around
and look at the
holot do you see the holot
yes do you see the geometric pattern the
fractal yes do you see where the lines
cross each other and where they don't
yes the idea is that where the lines
cross each other the most is what you
call the crystallization of energy down
into matter the idea is that the
relationship of those nodal points is
gravity do you understand this analogy
yes then there you go allow yourself to
understand how the noal points are
reflective of the Matrix in which the
material exists and you will understand
how to stretch and bend those nodal
points according to certain geometric
patterns such as Fibonacci
spirals so when you understand the idea
of Fibonacci Spirals and how they
overlap and create overlapping nodal
points and cross each other again and
again and again in certain ways and
expand in certain ways you will
understand everything you need to know
about the ideas of gravity about the
ideas of dark matter about the ideas of
dark energy and why what you call your
physical Universe seems to be
accelerating instead of slowing
down one example if you understand the
idea of taking a Fibonacci spiral in One
Direction and a Fibonacci spiral in the
opposite direction you will understand
that the spirals where they cross and
cross again and cross again and cross
again will be constantly farther and
farther and farther and farther and
farther apart yes correct well if you
understand that that's representative of
the expansion of your Universe you will
understand that that's why it's
accelerating because the idea of the
Spiral is it has to cover more distance
to reach the next nodal Point by being
that particular kind of curve it does so
and in your space-time reality that
translates out to the idea of Greater
distance over the same time equals
acceleration does that make sense yes
then there you go learn the V
vibrational state of those Fibonacci
spiral nodal points and you will
understand the relationship of gravity
to matter and you will understand the
idea of how to manipulate the vibrations
in order to manipulate gravity's
relationship to matter that's one way to
approach it there are several ways but
that's the way that we are talking about
right here in terms of the idea of
geometric
structure okay you you spoke about the
vibrational nature of um of matter just
now uh and that actually leads to my
second question oh all right so um when
we spoke you um you mentioned that in
order for for um a an object to go from
location a to location B yes all we
would need to do would be to change the
locational variable of the object itself
vibration location it is a frequency
within an energy equation a signature
vibration because location is not
somewhere that an object exists in
location is one of the properties of the
object and the object here and the
object here are actually two different
objects because of the change and
difference in the locational variable
within the overall energy equation of
that so-called object so in in the the
present day how can we measure that
vibrational frequency get a very very
very flat table that's at least 6 to 10
feet long very
flat take a very thin copper ball about
3 in 4 Ines in diameter Hollow very thin
as perfectly round as you can make it
put it at one end of the
table strike it and get it to vibrate or
vibrate it through some other means
measure those vibrations as precisely as
you can then move the ball to the other
end of the table and repeat that
measurement find the difference in those
two measurements if your instruments are
sensitive enough you will ultimately
discover the difference in those two
frequencies and when you do then you can
put the ball back in position a and then
either acoustically or
electromagnetically or any way you wish
bombard it overwhelm it in a sense with
the vibrational frequency that is
specific to the other end of the table
when the object was there and you will
see that the object will at least if not
disappear from here and wind up over
there instantaneously it will at least
roll across the table to its new
position and
stop and you will have begun to learn to
chart the idea of that vibrational
Matrix map which is what we use and
impose it over the idea of the physical
reality so that we understand like a c
chart what the vibrational coordinates
are for all the locations we wish to go
to thus then we isolate our ship in an
electromagnetic gravitational bubble
unlock it from any particular reality
impose upon it the vibrational location
equation of where we wish to go and thus
then when we remove the bubble pop we
disappear from there and pop we appear
at our destination ultimately you can do
it that way but begin with something
like this experiment and allow your
imagination to be your guide to alter it
in whatever way shape or form you so
desire but as soon as your instruments
are sensitive enough to tell the
difference in the vibration of an object
in two different locations you'll be on
your way to charting the vibrational map
of the
universe Perfect all right all right
thank you thank you